{
    "id": "d000346b712f4afab546553b1747f440",
    "title": "Questions And Negatives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She …………………. want to be disturbed while she is working.",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, we make negatives by putting do not or does not before the infinitive. We use does not when the subject is a singular noun or pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "does not",
                "do not",
                "has not"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a4d3713c032e47eeb84766631441a9bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ………………… returned the camera you borrowed from me.",
            "description": "The past participle 'returned' clearly indicates that we need have, not do, here.",
            "answers": [
                "has not",
                "did not",
                "have not"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f9b36c59a3e24cff85f7908cfebb8a52"
        },
        {
            "question": "Michael ………………… speak French.",
            "description": "We use ‘does not’ here because Michael is a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "do not",
                "does not",
                "has not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9dd31de052fe4eb4987e7d638ad03961"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you ………………. the parcel last week?",
            "description": "After do and does we use the infinitive (first form of the verb). Did + send -> sent",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "send"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e10b5d5d5c3343d08d1876a45aacde92"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………….. the meeting yesterday.",
            "description": "The present perfect tense cannot be used with past time expressions.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't attend",
                "haven't attended",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "58096f29fc0e46e886b7d1bdda7984e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "She buys a lot of things she ………………",
            "description": "We use does with singular nouns and pronouns. Also, we use the simple present to talk about habits. ",
            "answers": [
                "do not want",
                "does not want",
                "has not wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "514209ade2954981990ee6c2f50406c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. you injure yourself while playing football yesterday?",
            "description": "The auxiliaries do and have are used in the present tenses. ",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Did",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9341c30e161c4995b3e9ad1b7c086a93"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where could .....................… at this hour of the night?",
            "description": "In questions, only the first of the two auxiliaries goes before the subject.",
            "answers": [
                "have she gone",
                "she have gone",
                "she have went"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fda128a340e0439e974a5bc16ff5ce74"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… I told you not to be late?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Didn't",
                "Haven't",
                "Don’t"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1582c92d61ea46fca50fd5d54c4731cc"
        },
        {
            "question": "They …………………. tabulated the marks yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not",
                "have not",
                "do not"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "16ae6081c0704058b3164c7e391e3bae"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you been ………………. for long?",
            "description": "In the present perfect continuous tense, we use has/have + been + ing form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "waiting",
                "waited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d24625bb5e342ca8328234eaf863740"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul ………………. the test in the first attempt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not pass",
                "has not pass",
                "does not pass"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f59cac2c8de1450f9d6af1f0e1bc7344"
        }
    ]
}